Guide to the International Woodworkers of America Local 3-101 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Woodworkers of America Local 3-101 records, 1940-1983; 3120-002; 7.97 cubic feet (6 boxes)
  - MINUTES, 1946-1980; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/3-1/26)
    - Local 3-101 (Everett) - Regular Meetings - Attendance Lists and Minutes (Minutes span from 1969 to 1972 only), 1962-1972 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Regular Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Regular Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Regular Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Regular Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Local Meetings - Copies, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Meetings, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Meetings - Copies, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Meetings, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Meetings, 1962-1961 (Box-folder 1//15)
    - Meetings - Copies, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Meetings, 1960 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Meetings - Copies, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Meetings, 1957 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Meetings, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Meetings, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Meetings, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Meetings, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Meetings, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Negotiations with Reinell Boats Inc., 1972 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - WAGE SCALES, 1944-1953; SERIES III (Box-folder 2/1-2/17)
    - Wage Scales, April 1944 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Wage Scales, April 1944 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Wage Scales, April 1944 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Wage Scales, April 1944 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Wage Scales, April 1944 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Pacific Northwest Fir and Pine Area Wage Scale Book (Part 1 of 4), December 1950 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Pacific Northwest Fir and Pine Area Wage Scale Book (Part 2 of 4), December 1950 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Pacific Northwest Fir and Pine Area Wage Scale Book (Part 3 of 4), December 1950 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Pacific Northwest Fir and Pine Area Wage Scale Book (Part 4 of 4), December 1950 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - IWA Studies on Minimum Classification Wage Rates and Comparative Logging Wage Data, 1953 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Wage Scales (part 1 of 3), January 1952 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Wage Scales (part 2 of 3), January 1952 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Wage Scales (part 3 of 3), January 1952 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Wage Scales - copies, January 1952 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Wage Scales - copies (part 1 of 3), January 1952 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Wage Scales - copies (part 2 of 3), January 1952 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Wage Scales - copies (part 3 of 3), January 1952 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - JOB DESCRIPTIONS, circa 1955-circa 1975; SERIES IV: (Box-folder 2/18-2/23)
    - Operating Millwright, Construction Millwright, Electrician, Pipe Department, Mechanist, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Power House, Paint and Lubrication, Filers, Watchmen, Pondman, Sawmill B., 1955-1975 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Sawmill C., Green Chains, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Planing Mill, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Kilns, Shipping, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Pulp Chips, Cleanup, Pres-To-Log, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - NEGOTIATIONS AND AGREEMENTS, 1969, 1972, 1973, 1981; SERIES V: (Box-folder 2/24)
  - GRIEVANCES, 1975-1980; SERIES VI: (Box-folder 2/25-2/30)
    - Scot Negotiation Points, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Cascade Handle Co., 1977 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Wholesale and Door, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Scott Paper Grievances - Hamilton Camp - Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Scott Paper Grievances - Granite Falls Camp, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Assorted, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - PUBLICATIONS - "A Guide to Labor Legislation: For Supervisors and Shop Stewards", 1944-1945; SERIES VII (Box-folder 3/1-3/2)
    - PUBLICATIONS - "A Guide to Labor Legislation: For Supervisors and Shop Stewards" (part 1 of 2), 1944-1945 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - PUBLICATIONS - "A Guide to Labor Legislation: For Supervisors and Shop Stewards" (part 2 of 2), 1944-1945 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD MINUTES 1955-1974, 1978-1980, SERIES VIII (Box-folder 3/3-3/15)
    - Minutes, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Minutes - Copies, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Minutes, 1955 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Minutes, 1956 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Minutes, Membership Lists, 1957 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Minutes, Membership Lists, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Minutes, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - SHOP STEWARDS COUNCIL. Minutes and Attendance List, 1965-1968, 1972; SERIES IX: (Box-folder 3/16)
  - WOOD PRODUCTS SAFETY COMMITTEE, 1976-1983; SERIES X: (Box-folder 3/17-3/20)
    - Minutes and Interoffice Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Minutes, Safety Coordinator Reports, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Workers Compensation Report, Accident Reports, Safety Rules, 1976, 1983 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Minutes, WCB News (May-June 1977), Accident and Injuries Reports, Industrial Hygiene Reports, Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - PUBLISHERS FOREST PRODUCTS COMPANY (ANACORTES) BRANCH., 1970-1980; SERIES XI (Box-folder 3/21-3/27)
    - Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Minutes, Negotiations, Grievances and other related files., 1971-1980 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Manager Level Meetings, Superintendent Meetings, Standing Committee Meetings, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Grievances, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Grievances, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 3/27)
  - WEYERHAUSER STANDING COMMITTEE., November 15 1940-1983; SERIES XII (Box-folder 3/28-6/18)
    - Minutes, November 15 1940-1979; Subseries A (Box-folder 3/28-4/13)
      - Minutes, 1964 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Minutes, 1963 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Minutes, August-November 1961, 1962 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Minutes, February-April, August-October 1966 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 3/32)
      - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - Minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Minutes, December 28 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Minutes, Union Minutes, November 15 1940-July 19 1944, September-October 1960 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Minutes, Union Minutes, July 19 1944-March 14 1946 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Union Minutes, March 15 1946-March 28 1950 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Union Minutes, April 19 1950 - March 9 1952, April 23 1953-December 16 1953 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Union Minutes, May 13 1959-June 7 1961 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Union Minutes, September 5 1956-May 6 1959 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Union Minutes, May 26 1954-August 31 1956 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Negotiations, 1955; Subseries B (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Grievances, 1960-1980; Subseries C (Box-folder 4/15-5/12)
      - Grievances, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Grievances, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Grievances, 1974 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Grievances - Information Sheets, 1974 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Grievances, 1975 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Grievances - Information Sheets, 1975 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Grievances, 1977 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Grievances, 1977 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Grievances, 1978 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Grievances, 1978 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Grievances, 1978 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Grievances, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Grievances, 1976 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Grievances, 1980 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Grievances, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Grievances, 1979 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Grievances, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Grievances, 1972 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Grievances, 1973 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Job Postings-[By Department], 1977-1983; Subseries D (Box-folder 5/13-6/14)
      - Yard, Shipping, 1982 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Planing Mill, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Mill E., Maintenance, 1982 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Planing Mill, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Mill E., 1981 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Yard, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Maintenance, Shipping, Pond, Filing, 1981 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Mill E., 1979 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Planing Mill, 1979 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Maintenance, Shipping, Yard, 1979 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Chip, Pond and Yard, Clean-Up, Presto-Logs, 1979 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Presto-Log, Mill E., 1980 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Shipping, 1980 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Yard-Kiln, 1980 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Planing Mill, 1980 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Pond, Filing, 1980 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Mill B., Shipping, Maintenance, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Mill E., Planing Mill, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Clean Up, Files, Pond, Yard, Presto-Logs, 1978 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Yard and Kilns, Shipping, 1983 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Mill E., 1983 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Planing Mill, 1983 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Maintenance, 1983 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Job Postings (Part 1 of 2), 1977 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Job Postings (Part 2 of 2), 1977 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Wage Scales, 1973-1976; Subseries E (Box-folder 6/15-6/18)
      - Wage Scales, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Wage Scales, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - Wage Scales, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - Wage Scales, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6/18)